Promises made, promises kept. It's time.
[sighs]
Here we go. Finally. I know. I know. I'm
sorry it's taken a little bit longer.
Should have done it a day ago.
Enough about women's rights. It is
>> I agree.
I'm already on board. True.
I'm sick of hearing about it.
It's
>> time to talk about women's wrongs. We
are always talking about how adult
content has fried the male brain and we
have talked about how romance novels
have fried the female brain in a similar
way. But there is a unique brain frying
happening over on Tik Tok and it has
caused probably the greatest gender
divide I have ever seen on any culture
war topic ever. It's one of the very
>> so far
>> very few times I've genuinely been taken
aback by something on the internet. And
if you know me, that should worry you.
Many Republican women and mostly
Democrat women are finally coming
together. They're putting their
differences aside over what you may ask.
>> You are never going to kill Lindsy
Clancy.
[cheering]
>> Female Tik Tok psychosis. That's about
right.
>> Man dating a woman. Ask her about the
Lindsay Clancy trial. And if she says
she feels bad for her or even worse, the
husband did it. Yeah.
>> Run. Yes. The women are rising up to
defend Lindsay Clancy, a woman who
brutally took out her own three
children. Lindsay admitted she did it.
Her lawyers admitted she did it. All
evidence lines up and proves she did it.
The current trial debate was not about
if she did it or not. The current trial
is about whether she will be thrown in
prison for murder or thrown in a looney
bin for being crazy. As I am recording
this right now, the jury has not decided
yet. This video is less about the case
itself, and more about the discourse
surrounding it, the insane theories
people are coming up with to defend this
woman, the bizarre fanfiction they are
writing about husband, how they have
donated over $1 million for her, and all
of the real life protests happening to
support her. OJ Simpson for white women.
Now, not all women are defending Lindsay
Clancy, obviously, but nearly all of the
people defending her. Like 99.99%
of the people defending her are women.
So, what exactly is going on here? Why
are thousands
>> women are programmed to do that? That's
why it's just that simple.
>> Of women supporting this woman who has
done a terrible, horrible thing. Do
these women know something? I don't
know. Did the husband actually do it?
this damning evidence that only these
Tik Tok detectives found out.
>> No. No. These people are crazy. These
people are freaks. Let's talk about it.
Let's watch some crazy Tik Toks and read
some delusional comments. Let's talk
about why repeal the 19th was trending
on Twitter for 3 days. And let's take a
comprehensive look into what I'm calling
mass female Tik Tok psychosis. That's
right. Women are remembering that
believing [clears throat] another woman
>> Uhhuh. is the start to changing the
world. Before we dive into this
insanity, let's quickly give a shout out
to today's sponsor, a tool that can help
you navigate through all the insanity of
women are believing other women have
been using for 6 years now.
>> Ground News.
>> Uh-huh.
>> Ground News is a website and an app that
lets you see how news stories are being
covered all across the political
spectrum from left, right, and center.
Every story comes with a quick visual
breakdown of the political bias,
ownership, and headlines that helps you
understand
and make sure you're getting both sides.
>> The reason why they talk with the
annoying accents is that they all think
that they're starring in a TV show where
they're the star and the most important
person. And so their entire worldview is
centered around being perceived in a
certain way. So they're dramatic because
they feel like they're part of some sort
of event that's larger than themselves.
They make it easy to compare headlines
to see how political bias and media
ownership can affect the framing of a
story. For example, let's take a look at
this story about how Democrats are
facing pressure to address Hassan
Piker's controversial comments on Jewish
Americans because American politics
apparently revolves around a Twitch
streamer. Now, on the left, you'll see
headlines covering the story like
corporate Democrats ripped for attacks
on anti-Zionist Hassan And this
is how a right-wing outlet covered the
same exact story. Hassan brags Els
is faking moderation to scam voters.
Same event, completely different focus,
completely different vibe. It sounds
like they're covering two different
stories. The ground news feature I use
the most is definitely the blind spot
tool. It shows you news that has been
covered by one side of the political
spectrum but ignored by the other. For
example, here is a story about how Trump
posts truth social ranking of 34
presidents and put himself in first
place.
I've just I do have to say that like as
funny as he is, you you have to admit
that h not having Trump as president,
there's a lot of baggage, man. He's
really funny, but it's like, man, he
really does some dub bro. Like,
yeah,
>> 25 sources covered this. 63% were
leftwing and only 25% were right-wing.
Probably because it's a little
embarrassing. Here is a story about how
Homeland Security is warning of Chinese
parts in election machines and will
require paper ballot audits. 16 sources
covered this, all of them right-wing.
I've been using Ground News for years
now, and it is my go-to app to read the
news. But don't just take my word for
it. Even the Nobel Peace Center
recognized ground news as an excellent
way to stay informed, avoid echo
chambers, and expand your world view.
Hi, that's our president.
I am currently offering 40% off their
Vantage plan, which is the plan I use to
access China's promotion to cover it.
>> To get the 40% off discount
or use the QR code on screen right here
or click the link in the video
description down below to subscribe to
their Vantage plan today. Huge thank you
to Ground News for sponsoring this
video. Now, let's get back into it. I
know you were all waiting for this
video. I'm [clears throat] sorry. I
wanted to take my sweet time with it. I
know a lot of you have seen me crashing
the out on Twitter about this.
Well, I got my emotions out of the way.
Mostly logic is seeping in. I am more
angry than ever before. Uh, so I am
ready. If you are not familiar with this
trial or what is going on, here is a
quick rundown. In January 2023, Lindsay
Clancy, a former labor and delivery
nurse and mother of three, crazy that
you'd be like, 5-year-old Cora,
three-year-old Dawson, and 8-month-old
Ken. On the evening of January 24th,
Lindsay Clancy purposely sent her
husband, Patrick Clancy, out on a long
errand. She told him to pick up
medication at CVS and pick up food from
a restaurant far away. And while he was
gone, she took each of her children, one
by one, down to the basement and
strangled them to death with exercise
ropes. Wow.
>> She then tried to take the coward's way
out by jumping out a two-story window.
>> What a dumb
>> She's now paralyzed in a wheelchair. The
defense argues that Lindsay was
suffering from postpartum psychosis. We
will get into that. And that she wasn't
receiving the help she needed. We'll get
into that, too. Trust me, we will get
into all that. But as it stands right
now and as it stood for years, it is
universally accepted that Lindsay Clancy
killed her children. The trial was about
if Lindsay was going to prison or the
Looney Bin. Nobody in the court is
>> The problem is that the Looney Bin can
let you out. That's the big issue. Like
I'd be okay with her going to the looney
bin if it meant a life sentence. Like
you're you're stuck inside of the crazy
box and you're never coming out of the
box. The problem is that you can come
out of the box.
>> Arguing that Lindsay Clancy is innocent.
Not even her own lawyer. Nobody. Well,
nobody except thousands and thousands of
women on TikTok.
>> Lindsay Clancy didn't do it. Patrick
Clancy.
>> Look at her lips.
Oh my god.
Holy Look at that.
That's crazy. You see that?
What the is going on here?
>> Do it.
>> Patrick Clancy did that. He drugged
Lindsay.
>> He did it. Just he did it. Like read
everything. Look at everything. Don't
hate women.
>> Believe all women. And I have to say
also that and this is important and I
can say this right. We have LTG to do
the other side but I have to do this
one. It's mostly white women that are
doing this. It is it's mostly white
women that are doing this. And do you
know why? One of the big reasons why is
because a lot of white guys put up with
this.
Fat white women. Yep. That's right. It's
because guys are putting up with it.
my kids. No, you didn't. For some
reason, every woman and her mother has
convinced herself that actually
Lindsay's husband, Patrick, is the real
perpetrator of this crime. Despite there
being absolutely no proof of this,
nobody thinks whatsoever. Lindsay Clancy
is innocent. The husband did it. I said
what I said. New theory. He killed the
kids. His was the voice she heard. He
threw her out the window. She's about to
be jailed for life for something her
husband did. He was having an affair. He
plotted. I think she like god damn, bro.
Like, is lizard an ethnicity?
Can Can you ethnically be a lizard?
Well, yeah, I guess so, cuz there's Mark
Zuckerberg.
>> He drugged her. I think the voices she
was hearing was him. Her surviving
wasn't part of his plan. I think he was
already having an affair. He killed his
kids and attempted to kill her, then
blamed her for what he actually did. I
think he did it while she was in severe
psychosis and convinced her she did it.
I have the strangest feeling that he was
having an affair with one of her
doctors. I just can't prove it.
>> I just can't prove it. We know. We know,
sweetie. Look at her sitting in the
passenger seat with the kid in the car.
Oh my god, that poor little kid.
>> It never happened. It never happened. We
made this one up.
>> Yeah,
>> it's fiction.
>> Yeah. Yeah. None of that they said
is true. None of it. Not a single thing
they said is based in reality. My theory
is, and I could be wrong, is that yes,
you are wrong. I am not reading the
rest. This all happened years ago. They
investigated the husband and found
nothing. But you see, the dozens of
professionals working on this case, the
detectives, the FBI, the cops, the
lawyers are nothing compared to the mind
of the tick tock female. They can see
through it all. Evidence be damned. The
husband did it, and they can prove it
with intuition and vibes and star
racism. If women's intuition was as good
as they think it is, then they wouldn't
keep ending up with these guys
that they have to get restraining orders
from and freaking out about. Everybody
knows these guys are awful women. The
entire idea that women's intuition is
this kind of like six sense. Uh it it's
not. Okay, let's just say that it's not.
>> And what is your date of birth?
>> June 15th, 1988.
>> Oh, he's 2 years older than me. He did
it.
>> You know, just [clears throat] following
all their birth chart.
>> Oh, June. He was born in Oh, he's a
Gemini
>> charts and birthdays and zodiac signs.
>> Another white woman.
>> I've already gone over the forensic
astrology charts that show that the
perpetrator is a male.
>> I'm telling you all right now, when the
South Node goes into Cancer,
>> overwhelmingly, South Node goes into
Cancer. Cancer. In March of 2028, the
south node is going to transit over
Patrick Clancy's moon in cancer.
>> Gemini stellium with cancer stellium
gives massive manipulator energy. If
there's a Gemini male involved, there's
a 99% chance he's guilty. If he's Gemini
and she's a Leo, it was toxic between
them. He did it. That's all I needed to
know. Leos don't kill their cubs. Leos
don't kill. Geminis do. Your honor, he
was a Gemini. Death. This is
This is why we had the witch trials.
This is why we did it.
Isn't it crazy that it took us 400
years?
But
wow. Right.
Wow.
Wow. I learned that the lawyer in this
Clancy trial is an Aquarius. This is the
most Saturn thing I have seen.
>> This is the All right, I have to use the
bathroom. Give me a minute. I I I just I
have to make sure I'm completely focused
on this nose ring. Well, that's what
they usually do to hogs and cows. I'm
back.
I'm sorry, gentlemen.
Septum piercing witch. Yeah, that's kind
of what they are. I think that's
accurate. Sure.
Oh man.
>> In a long time.
>> The most Saturn thing you have seen in a
long What? What does that mean? By the
way, that nose ring looks like Sorry.
Sorry. Was that Uranus of me to say?
>> I think the voices Lindsay Clancy was
hearing in her head were her husband's
thoughts. Women when they are
postpartum.
>> They all have nose rings, too. You see
that?
Like livestock.
are more psychically intuitive and
telepathic.
>> Women have intuition. So many of us are
standing behind Lindsay because we know
she didn't do it. As women, we know what
he did. We see it. Women know. We all
know. It's Patrick Clancy versus the
Women of America at this lol. Like,
>> and and by the way, look at look at
this. This is what's so crazy. 79,000
likes.
>> Oh my god.
>> Lol. Like, why hasn't he been arrested
yet? Oh my god. Because the law isn't
based on emotions and Tik Tok girlies
gut feelings, but rather uses evidence,
testimonies, digital footprints, and
most important confessions to deter out
of here.
>> Says the man. Women
>> says the man.
Yeah.
They're like kids.
>> Intuition. Men do not. Women need to
lead the FBI. No, because women's
intuition is powerful. Women have all
this magical intuition until it comes to
finding a good man and then all their
exes are abusive narcissists.
>> Exactly. exactly. Women's
intuition is garbage. Okay. Total
garbage.
>> Weird how that works out. How do we know
Patrick Clancy did it?
>> It's exactly what I said.
>> Just look at him. He just looks like
>> it's not pre-washed. It's just the way
it is.
>> Case closed. This is the biggest reason
I don't just how it is.
>> Without knowing anything about it, but
seeing what the man looks like, he did
it. My three-year-old daughter
>> say
>> took one look at him and said, "That's a
bad guy." His facial expressions are
giving away. He's never shown any grief
over losing his three children. Lindsay,
on the other hand, is going through
hell. Not a single tear stone face the
whole time. Something is off. Something
seems off about him. Yeah, his wife
murdered his children. That's what's
off, you freaks. The 911 call was so
horrific, so traumatizing that they
didn't want it released to the public.
>> That's exactly why they should have
released it.
I hate how everything now has been
sterilized.
Like people won't say kill, they won't
say murder, they won't say rape, they
won't say pedophile.
They won't say the words that describe
the actions and describe the intent.
Trigger pullers instead of shooters.
Everything has been like re it's
basically been redefined to be less
upsetting.
It's such a huge problem.
>> Quickly ask you about the Patrick Clancy
911 call because when Patrick Clancy
arrived at the house, found his wife
outside, had jumped from the window, and
then found the kids inside, there was
this awful 911 call that has not been
played publicly. But you have heard the
call. It was one of the worst pro the
worst thing I've ever heard. It was the
screams coming out of Patrick were just
unearly and guttural and
>> unlike anything I've ever heard
>> because you hear him screaming and you
hear him say Dawson and my buddy and
then he goes to the other side of the
basement where there's a den and you
hear him find Kora and he screams baby.
Then you can hear when he finds talent.
Um because the the pain in his voice
gets him.
>> But yeah, he's not crying in court like
they do in the movies. So he's guilty
because everyone knows crying in court
means you're innocent, right? And you
know damn well that if he was crying,
they would all just say he's
>> they would just say he's manipulating or
faking it. Yeah. It doesn't matter. Like
again, you never Exactly. You never
accept any of their framing
>> it, which they have. There was one point
in the trial where Patrick's voice was
shaky and he was getting upset and they
all were just like, "Well, narcissists
are really good actors, so if he doesn't
cry, he's a cold psychopathic Gemini.
And if he does cry, he's a narcissistic
actor." Also, I'm sorry, but if we're
going to judge people based on the way
they look, what the is this?
I know, you know, everybody knows.
We all know
she looks like a villain out of
a children's fairy tale. is a
goblin. is a ghoul. is a
Japanese water ghost. There are
thousands of woman triggered. The reason
because those are the eyes of a covert
narcissist. And we've all looked into
those eyes before. I've seen that same
look in my father's eyes. This photo of
him gives [laughter]
>> right unresolved personal trauma with
daddy. Oh, good.
>> Me the chills. You can actually feel the
rage he's trying to hide. Us women.
>> Yeah, I bet he's probably mad because of
the kids that got killed.
>> Dare down a man with those same kind of
eyes knowing he wanted to hurt us. Some
of the comments I'm getting are insane
because not just me, but women all over
the world who have lived with a
sociopathic psycho clock Patrick
immediately. These women are all
projecting their daddy issues and like
past relationship trauma onto this
randoming guy. This guy who just went
through like unimaginable horror and
they're just like, he reminds me of my
dad.
>> I don't believe Patrick did anything for
Lindsay. I think Lindsay did it all
herself. I don't think he was a good
father. I don't think he was a good
husband. I think. I think. Who the
are you? Who cares what you think? Did
you know this man personally? No, you
didn't. How about instead of trauma
dumping on the internet, you go to
therapy.
>> All right. He did it. Patrick did it.
Patrick's the one.
>> I remember seeing this one.
>> Did it. I was actually in therapy today
and my therapist and I were talking
about it and she looks at me and she
goes, "He did it.
>> Oh god, never mind. Maybe therapy is not
a good idea."
>> Therapy is a horrible idea. I think
therapy is a joke.
So, if you're a girl and you're unhappy,
you need to just go to church. If you're
a guy and you're unhappy, you need to
start a project that requires physical
effort and activity.
And if that doesn't work, just you you
go to the mental asylum.
There's just something wrong with you.
That's it.
assen chat GPT ass therapists just
enabling and feeding the delusion of
these narcissistic idiots. You know what
a real therapist would say? You know
what a real good therapist would say?
Log off. Also, I miss when everyone's
lips didn't look like prolapsed
Like, get that out of here. I'm
sick of it.
>> Therapist. Yeah. It's like it's crazy
how like I mean women that get like lip
filler and other like I get like I mean
if women want to get plastic surgery I
mean I think you should be able to do
what you want but you are going to look
usually like an idiot. There's a lot of
women that get plastic surgery and they
look better but the ones that don't you
can easily tell
>> want to see it. There is no proof that
Patrick Clancy was a abusive husband or
a bad father. In fact, there's only
proof of the opposite. Things we do know
from this case was that Patrick was a
very helpful father. He did paternity
leave. He worked from home. He took the
kids whenever she wanted him to. Paid
the bills. He let her stay home. They
had a nanny. But no, he's actually a
terrible father. And he's guilty because
of mystical rectangle. So,
>> this is rock bottom for her.
>> Oh, that's what she did to the kids.
She's hit her worst, but there's going
to be more that comes out regarding him.
Did Patrick unal alive the children?
>> It's all white women. It is. It's all
white women. And I'm sure there's going
to be a couple of exceptions, but man,
you guys got to see the trend.
And it it's our fault.
It's our fault because we don't ever
tell them no.
This is why we need robots so men don't
feel like they have to capitulate to
this stupidity.
>> Dumb ass.
[laughter]
>> Ah, yes. The A of apples. Mhm.
>> You are gay.
>> I have decided I'm going to send Lindsay
Clancy a letter of encouragement.
>> I was at the salon this morning getting
my hair done and every woman in the
place believes she's innocent and PC is
responsible.
>> Patrick Clancy,
>> grandmas, young gals, all of them. I
hope Lindsay knows we are pulling for
her. All women stand with Lindsay. Even
if she did it, she didn't do it. Even if
he didn't do it, he did it. What
>> what what they mean is that it's never a
woman's fault and it's always a man's
fault. That's it. Why are so many people
calling this out saying women are crazy?
But every time a black American's on
trial, it's the system. One is gendered,
the other one's race. They're equal the
same. It's dumb all around. It's
tribalism. Well, it's just it's a
different excuse, right? That's it. It's
just a different excuse. It's crazy how
many teeth people are supposed to have,
isn't it? It's always a shock for me to
see that. Like, wow. Really?
>> She was their mother before she became a
headline. Oh, wow. Why did she become a
headline?
>> Because she killed them.
>> Tell the class. Those children had a
childhood because of their mother.
>> And now the
>> have no adulthood because of their
mother.
>> Yeah.
>> Your point. It sounds absolutely crazy,
but I've got this overwhelming feeling
that she's part of the awakening of the
divine feminine. We are all
>> I agree. I think that this is the
awakening. This is this is a the tr so
this is step like point0
um in the multi-step plan of never you
know what
>> rallying around her except for those of
us who are still under the patriarchy. I
will add to this and tell you that I too
have been getting
>> patriarchy is going to come back and
everybody's gonna be like oh my god why
did it take so long?
>> Sensational downloads. I honestly feel
as though this woman is not only going
to have an awakening, but she's going to
be found innocent. The patriarchy
thought we would think of her as a
monster, but so many women are seeing
themselves in her. The divine feminine
frequency coming through. Lindsay Clancy
is being protected. Doing a justice
spell for Lindsay Clancy, cuz I know the
truth will come.
>> Doing a justice spell. And it's a stupid
middle-aged woman trying to set a wine
glass on fire on her stove.
Yeah, that's about right.
Got it.
>> Out and the real villain will be
revealed. Patrick Clancy has pissed off
the witches.
>> Everyone,
>> we know
>> of us that have roots that go back to
the Salem witch trials. We are freeing
our ancestral bloodline by coming
together for Lindsay Clancy.
>> Yeah. By proving them right.
>> Salem witch trials really that bad?
Y'all are pissing me off.
You're pissing me off about this Lindsay
Clancy case. We're the ones that are
trying to figure out who actually did
this to these poor ass innocent
children.
>> What do you mean you're the ones trying
to figure out who DID IT? THEY KNOW
>> she's just a fat woman that probably
doesn't have a job. Spends all day at
home and so she's got to have something
to do to make herself feel good.
>> Who did it? You are not the people
actually working on the They know that,
right? They know they're not actually
working on the case, right?
>> We literally binge watch true crime as a
hobby. We've been trained for this
moment. Clocking in for my shift as an
at home juror on the Lindsay Clancy
trial. Day 14. This
>> day 14. That's right. See, it's just
they don't even do anything.
>> Me feeling like I'm on Law and Order
with all you guys. Coffee. For those of
us working hard on this case, we deserve
coffee and bonus pay. God,
>> you're working on the case.
>> I really think they're working on this
case. You were not detectives. You are
bored housewives who replace daytime.
>> Why is it that the collective the the
collective paos or I don't know
the collective conscience of all these
women is like a like a 9-year-old.
Have you guys ever noticed this that
like the their collective conscience is
equivalent to like what a nine-year-old
would think or do or say?
Isn't that weird? Like what are the odds
of that?
operas with Tik Tok. Again, I can't
stress this enough. The trial is not
about who did it. They really do believe
that this is like a movie and there's
going to be some kind of plot twist that
the defense will have like his L. Woods
moment. Thousands and thousands of women
blindly repeating the same talking
points. He cheated on her. No, no
evidence. His DNA was on the exercise
bands. Well, yeah, because he tried to
untie them. He was literally at CVS when
this all He's on camera at CVS. They
literally have phone. They have all the
evidence.
>> Women online believe that he did it. He
ran a 4-minute mile to go home. Do it to
his own kids and stage it as if his wife
did it and fake a phone call while he
was with her while simultaneously
throwing her out of the building. And
then he ran a 4-minute mile back and
then he got stuff from the store and
then he went to go pick up food and then
he came back and then he faked another.
>> Yes. Yes. That is what they actually
believe.
>> Lindsay Clancy trial. Have you guys been
following it?
>> My girlfriend has. I know nothing about
it, but she's on TikTok.
>> Oh, that poor guy.
>> For like 3 hours in the morning, she
thinks she's innocent.
>> If a woman kills her own kids, no matter
what the reason is, she should go to
jail.
>> Yeah, that's for sure.
>> That's for sure.
>> I feel like the husband could have been
more of a man.
>> Where do you get your news from? Just
curious.
>> Tik Tok.
>> He should go to jail for negligence. He
was He needs to take care of his kids.
>> Is this any of your girlfriends?
>> This is your girlfriend? Where are you
getting your news that the defense might
not be getting theirs?
>> Tik Tok. I just have seen a little bit
on Tik Tok.
>> I'm watching it on Tik Tok.
>> Tik Tockers are posting reenactment
videos of them hanging out the window to
prove that Lindsay Clancy is innocent.
>> You know, I'm starting to believe it's
no coincidence that every civilization
all over the world, even when they
didn't have any contact with each other,
all came to the same conclusion about
women. Also, why didn't Trump go through
with the banning Tik Tok thing? We would
be in a much better place right now.
Whatever.
>> I totally disagree.
The problem is women.
Tik Tok isn't the problem.
>> Happened with that. China doesn't even
let people consume slop like this. Maybe
they have the right idea. Maybe we got
to get a little Chinese Patrick Clancy
spotted with new wife amid ex-wife
Lindsay's murder trial. Imagine being
this guy. Imagine going through what he
has been through and now you have to
deal with retards on Tik Tok and TMZ
stalking you as if you were some kind of
pop star. Patrick was seen taking phone
calls and pacing in circles while using
his phone. At one point, he reportedly
sat with his feet on a table and wiggled
his toes. What?
>> Thank you, TMZ. That's just what we
needed to hear.
>> Okay. Also, this happened three years
ago, but I guess he's just never allowed
to move on and live a normal life. He
probably misses being a dad. He probably
misses having children. He probably
misses having a normal, stable life. I
don't know how this would functioning. I
would have gone full Shutter Island,
personally. And it's not like he just
moved on and forgot about them. He built
a park in their honor. He raised over
$75,000 for Boston's Children Hospital.
Also, Patrick and his sisters helped
create the Herd Foundation, which is an
organization that focuses on parental
mental health. That is way more than
these idiots supporting Lindsay ever
did. They could have donated to
charities or some but no, they
created a GoFundMe for Lindsay's family.
I donated 800 and I'm a single mom who
lives off ramen. I donated $5,000. If we
don't be her voice and get loud and
fight for her justice until Patrick is
in prison for the rest of his life, then
we will have failed as a nation. And if
this can happen to her, it can happen to
any of us.
>> That's exactly the way that they look at
it. They think that they they want to
protect Lindsay Clansancy as a method of
kind of proxy for themselves. This is
generally the way that things go is that
it's not really about her as much as
it's like if they can do this to her,
then maybe this could happen to me.
>> Filming this, they have raised over $1
million for Lindsay. And I'm not
exaggerating when I tell you that every
single donation is from a woman. I'm not
joking. You can go check yourself. You
will be scrolling for a long ass time. I
scrolled for like 10 minutes and didn't
see one male name. Finally, women are
the protectors and providers protecting
a murderer and providing her with $1
million. But that's not all. It gets
worse. These women planned and organized
real life rallies outside of the
courthouse for
>> Look at that. It's beautiful.
[screaming]
>> [cheering and applause]
>> Wow.
>> I wonder what she thinks of this.
>> I mean, you've got to be out of your
mind atmosphere ever again.
Thank you.
>> We love you, [clears throat] Lindsay,
and we're here for you. We're here to
show support and love for her.
>> Very nice of them to do the strangle
hands pose in there.
>> They were waving at her, passing in the
car like she was the president of the
United States.
>> Yep. [cheering and applause]
They were like,
>> "It's all fat white women." I know.
>> Up in Giddily taking photos with
Lindsay's lawyer like he was some kind
of celebrity taking selfies in front of
the triple homicide court case.
>> Again, it's it's all it's all just the
ethos of a 9-year-old girl.
That's all it is. This is the collective
conscience of women on the internet is a
9-year-old girl.
What the A lot of these women
probably see this as nothing more than
like some bizarre form of super late
term post birth abortion. No matter what
you think of abortion, you got to admit
going from like safe legal rare to like
shout your abortion, just celebrating it
and completely normalizing it as if it's
like another form of birth control
probably had some bad side effects on
society. I don't know. I'm just throwing
out theories because like I have no
theory of mine for this. This is just
insane to me. I want to be charitable
and believe a lot of these women,
especially these mothers, just can't
fathom ever doing any of this to their
own children. So, they have to like cope
and make up theories. She would never do
that. She loved those kids. A mother
would never do that. It must have been
the husband. Women,
>> I think that to that extent, it's
probably true. But the problem to me is
that when you do something bad, it
doesn't really matter why you do it. It
just matters that it's happening. Like
I'm not really interested in like
hearing about like somebody's psychology
or about like why they feel this way. I
don't really give a honestly. I
only care about what you're doing. Like,
oh, you're doing this bad thing. Okay,
then you have to stop doing it. Like
that's literally it.
>> Deserve support and Lindsay didn't
>> receive the support that she deserved. A
lot of these women are projecting their
postpartum issues, their struggle with
motherhood onto Lindsay Clancy, which is
stupid. I'm not going to sugarcoat it
and be like, well, you know, they're
just stressed out and they they want to
martyr and whatever. No, it's stupid.
She's a murderer and she pre-planned all
of this. She just she needs to fry.
Like, [laughter]
I don't know what to say. This idea that
Lindsay Clancy was left hanging with no
support and no help is absolutely not
true. Lindsay had more help than most
women.
>> 99% of women. Her husband took paternity
leave so he can be home and more. He
took the kids when she needed a break.
Her parents were there to take the kids
when she needed a break. She had
nannies. She had nannies. She had a ton
of doctors trying to help her. She
checked her facility and voluntarily
checked herself out. Days later, Dr.
Gregory Satuff
>> testified that women and infants
hospital offered Lindsay Clancy help and
she denied it. help was offered to her
and she denied it. Like, what more could
have been done besides involuntarily
sending her to a looney bin, which I
support.
>> I wish that was possible to do. But
these
>> That's what we have to do.
And until we do this, we're going to
keep having these problems.
You can't let some chickens out of the
coupe, bro. [laughter] You can't let
them out, bro. Like,
they're crazy.
You got to keep them in the chicken coop
the moment that they get out. Like we
used to we had this bird and this bird
it name was birdie and whenever you let
birdie out of the cage [laughter] birdie
flies straight into a wall.
It's it was a cockatil. And my mom would
say, "OH, DON'T LET OH, WE GOING TO LET
HIM OUT." OH, THERE HE GOES. BOOM. IT'S
THE WALL. [laughter]
All right. Pick up birdie. put bird in
there. This is what would happen. And
you just don't you can't let him out of
the cage.
>> Women would not support that either.
They would say it was like denying her
freedom and agency and whatever. So like
what the do they want? Like are you
telling me right now that a bunch of
feminists are arguing that women's
hormones make them so crazy that they
should not have agency and they should
be locked up against their will? Okay.
>> I Yeah, I agree.
>> Two steps forward 150 years back. I
support mental illness in general is not
even an excuse. Many people who murder
are mentally ill. Probably most of them
are mentally ill. Like oh the woman who
murdered her three children was mentally
ill.
>> This changes everything. I thought she
was an upstanding normal citizen. Like
no.
>> We've learned a lot more about Lindsay
Clancy's [music] husband as this trial
has played out and women are clocking
every tidbit. We've learned a lot more
about Lindsay Clancy's husband. No, you
haven't. You watched some Tik Toks by
Pitbullmama 78 who told you about
Lindsay Clancy's husband with her tarot
cards and intuition and stupid
Shut the up. What the hell is going
on with women? They've developed pattern
recognition and can clock a problematic
man from a mile away. Cope.
>> No, you can't. [laughter] No, you can't.
You know you can't.
It's actually crazy like how bad women
are at picking partners. It is like I
I've known so many. It's like you just
keep you keep even ending up with losers
every single time
>> more. This woman used to be some like
right-wing libertarian podcaster by the
way. What the is going on? What is
really interesting about this and what
sets it apart from other things I've
covered is this is not political at all.
Like these aren't activists. This isn't
>> I'd argue that it is political. I think
that, you know, the recent polling where
there was a 40point difference between
Republicans and Democrats that
identified as such that thought that she
was uh guilty. I think that it's
overwhelmingly again mentally ill young
women. And what are mentally ill young
women? Most likely Democrats. They're
most likely Democrats. This is just the
way it is. So, and and you might not
like that, but it's just true.
like, you know, BLM or Luigi Manjone
where it was a political thing. This is
completely a-political to a lot of the
women. Literally, the woman who started
the first rally for Lindsay Clancy is
like a TPUSA, Charlie Kirk, Matt Walsh
fan. It's not just liberal women. It's
overwhelmingly liberal women, but it's
not just liberal women, which is so what
makes it a unique and creepy phenomenon.
There's also like no leftist men or
liberal men sticking their neck out for
these women. There's no like
performative male allies coming out like
I support you ladies.
>> Well, that's changed since this video
released.
>> I'm sorry. I'm sorry. There's one. Dear
fellow men, you are making us all look
like emotionally stunted meattheads over
this Lindsy Clancy thing. First of all,
fellow men,
>> yeah.
>> Are you a crab in a human skin suit?
Second of all, why should men give a how
they are perceived by insane women
supporting a baby murder? Oh, no. The
worst people on earth might think I'm a
meatthead.
>> What? Okay,
>> I made my thought.
>> This is what I was saying before about
how like thinking like a like a Floyd,
it's not unique to being a woman. There
are men that think like this too.
>> Clear on this. The moment that she um
was arrested, the moment that it made
the news, Lindsay Clancy is obviously
not guilty. There are a fleet of doctors
who should be imprisoned for what they
put her on. Not guilty is a very
interesting way to describe a woman who
literally admits to doing it, but okay.
Pop off, Candace. Tell us how Patrick
Clancy is also secretly a woman or
whatever the Next. Editing Shu
here. I just got to add the she's saying
about the fleet of doctors isn't really
true. It wasn't really the doctor's
fault. She kind of just doctor shopped
around for different pills. She never
told doctors she was seeing other
doctors. She didn't tell them she was on
other medications. and she kept just
collecting them, not taking them, taking
them whenever she wanted. The system
didn't fail her. And like one in five,
>> I think that's the dumbest Candace quote
of all time. I don't think it is.
I don't think it is. Like I know why
you'd think that, but I don't think that
it is. I think that there's been a lot
of other clips from Candace Owens that
are even dumber than that.
>> Them, taking them whenever she wanted.
The system didn't fail her. And like one
in five women are taking SSRIs. How many
have done that?
>> One in five non-Hispanic white women are
taking SSRIs.
>> Trust me, nobody hates big pharma more
than I do, but trying to make this a big
pharma thing isn't going to work here.
Not everything is big pharma, big
Israel, big state. And when I'm telling
you that, that's how you know it's bad.
Tommy Lauren of course came out with a
soft defense for this woman. I know a
lot of Republicans don't want to hear
this, but the right is on the verge of
making the same mistake with young women
that the left did with young men. I know
some of these women are fun to mock and
I get it and I do it too. But we have to
do better if we want to bring them over
to our side. If we totally alienate
young women, we will not win elections.
[music] We have to find a way to appeal
to them. If you guys remember the last
time I talked
>> Tommy Lauren is a and ultimately
she's going to advocate for women. She
was the same person that was she got
roasted for that. She is the only thing
that you if you want to appeal to women,
win. Just win. just be popular and win
and then have influence and power.
That's the only way you you can appeal
to women. Uh it doesn't m nothing else
matters. You can literally call them
You can call them You can
want to take their rights away and
they'll still support you if they think
that you're the person that's in
control. It's just the way they are.
>> About Tommy Lauren. It was responding to
her take about how men are all losers
who live in their mommy's basement.
That's why they're lonely and can't get
married. So, when it comes to men,
they're just losers in their mommy's
basements. But when it comes to women,
they're all perfect angels. Don't scare
them away. Like, what should the right
be doing to win over Lindsay Clansy's
supporters? Like, what? Like, why would
you even block them anyway? I don't
understand. My mother thinks Lindsay is
guilty. She's MAGA. Of course, I'm MAGA
and think Lindsay is innocent. Not all
of us are against Lindsay, you know. If
Lindsay was MAGA, you wouldn't support
her. The MAGA women behind Lindsay have
more of a backbone than liberals do
because we would support Lindsay even if
she was a liberal. You can't say the
same.
>> We're even like it's like I I don't know
which side in that circumstance is more
I don't even know. I I I can't parse
that out.
>> Ago women do not support. They do not
support Lindsay in any real meaningful
way.
>> Oh my god, dude. They're having a crazy
competition in the comments. I support
the baby murder more. No, I support the
baby murder more. Ladies, ladies, calm
down. You are both losing your voting
rights.
>> Men in the Lindsy Clancy comments, come
here. Come here. Shut the up.
Thousand trials going on every day where
men have done far worse.
>> These men in my comments do not say a
godamn word every other day when a man
annihilates his own.
>> Isn't it crazy how you already know what
their opinion is just by looking at
them?
>> Family. Men annihilate their families
all the time, yet you're not blaming old
men. What about men like Chris Watts?
Men do commit most of the murder. Men do
commit
>> men overwhelmingly do. Men are way more
violent than women are. Men are killers.
They're the ones that have started every
war, and they're probably the ones that
will start every war. They kill kids.
They kill women. They kill each other.
They kill animals. They kill dogs. They
kill civilizations. They blow up
buildings. They blow up cars. They do
everything.
It's not our fault, though. It's just
testosterone that makes us do this. So,
like, I don't know why you're trying to
hold us accountable. It's not like we're
doing this on purpose. It's just the way
that we're programmed.
>> Yeah. It's not our fault
>> of the family annihilation. But the
difference is, now stay with me here,
these men are not supported by thousands
of other men. They're not rallied around
and they're not given a million dollars.
These men are universally hated, as they
should be. as Lindsay Clancy should have
been. People aren't looking at Lindsay
and going, "Wow, all women are
murderers. They're looking at all the
women supporting the murderer." And it's
funny they bring up Chris Watts, a guy
who was in prison for murdering his wife
and children when it wasn't men who
supported Chris Watts. It was women. A
ton of women sent love letters.
>> He's locked up for rice. So why do women
send him love letters?
>> There's two Chris Watts. This is more of
female intuition at work and his wife
and children. This is how I know Patrick
Clancy is innocent because if he wasn't,
all these women would be thirsting after
him like they do every other murder.
Now, this case has tested many
relationships.
>> If Patrick Clansancy looked like Henry
Cavl, people would want Lindsey Clancy
to get the electric chair. If Lindsey
Clancy looked like Sydney Sweeney, all
the women would also want Lindsey
Clansancy to get the electric chair.
It's actually that simple.
I know. I know. I know. You might think
to yourself, "There's no way."
Yep.
It's that simple.
>> At first, my husband didn't understand
why I was so invested in this trial.
Then he tried to start making me see
things from a different perspective, and
now he's sleeping upstairs. My boyfriend
is on Reddit and they're calling people
on TikTok crazy for saying it was
Patrick and he doesn't believe me and
I'm like, "Do you want to break up right
now, bro? Broke up with my boyfriend
last night over this case. I can't stop
crying, but I know I did the right
thing." His loss, you deserve better.
Never settle for less than he did it,
ladies. Literally got in a fight with my
boyfriend of 6 years over this. He's
convinced she did it, and he kept trying
to pester me into explaining why I think
she did it. And all I could answer is,
"You're not a woman. You don't
To the extent that you engage in a
political conversation with a female,
you've already lost the correct frame of
reference.
You've you've lost by default.
like you're having a conversation with
them about [snorts]
uh like a legal matter or a uh a court
case or like immigration or something.
This is you you do not even
do not even engage in this because you
don't want to encourage this type of
thinking.
It's problematic. It's confusing.
It's complex. It's upsetting
those guys. No, no. The thing is that
you know what she said? I was expl I
took her out to dinner, of course, and
I was explaining to her why people in
America were crazy and I was talking
about Charlie Kirk and she goes, "Who's
Charlie Kirk?"
She didn't even know.
She had no idea
that is not when was this? It's like a I
don't know. It was like a month ago or
something.
>> Get it. No, because that is so valid. We
are tuned into these kind of things in a
way men are not. The way they just
enable the worst in each other never
will cease to amaze me. Oh my god,
you're so valid. Queen,
>> break up with your man for not
supporting a murderer. Yeah. Also,
boyfriend of six years.
Yeah,
>> I'm considering calling off my
>> Yeah, true. Like, if you have a
boyfriend for more than 2 years and
you're dating for more than two years
and you're a woman, you need to break up
with him because he's just stringing you
along until we can find a better woman
to get in a relationship with and get
married to. I am a traditional marriage
enjoyer. I think that's exactly what you
should do. And women only have a finite
period of time in which they're
appealing to men. It's really not very
long. And men on the other hand have a
much longer window in which they can be
appealing to to women. So what men do in
a lot of cases is they string women
along for multiple years being in a
relationship with them, never actually
committing to them. And then you know
whenever this woman is like 29 years old
or she's 31 years old and she's a hag
now, basically now they break up and
she's going to start back at square one.
That's it.
It It's a It No, no, really. Like, it's
a huge problem that women have and
nobody ever talks about this, but it's
like men waste women's most prime years
in situationships and then these women
get older and they're not as appealing
to men and they hate all men. And it's
like, honestly, guys, I don't think you
should be doing that. I think I don't
think you need to be around in
four different situationship. No good.
They deserve it. I don't think so. Why
do you believe in marriage? Because it's
the best thing for the kids. I don't
give a about like the man and the
woman and whether they're in love or
not. Who gives a about that? That's
It's gay. But like what really
matters is about the civility of the
family for the child. And if you build a
culture and you build a society that
doesn't put children first, that is a
society that dies. That's the reason why
I believe in it. It has nothing to do
with men or women or custody or anything
else. What matters is the kid. And if
you're not putting kids first, you have
a sick society.
That's the way I look at it.
>> Wedding next year because of this. He's
a good man, but he said something about
the women outside the court for Lindsay
that really rubbed me the wrong way and
I couldn't get over it. What did he say
about the women outside the courtroom?
He said they all looked like crazy
Karens.
>> My boy.
There you go. There you go.
What do you think about a dysfunctional
couple that can't make it work? Break
up. Break up and find somebody else.
>> Pulling off a wedding to a good man
because he dared called these freaks
Karens. Holy dude dodged a nuclear bomb.
This whole phenomenon makes a lot more
sense when you realize just how deeply
true crime has infested female culture.
Women are significantly more likely than
men to consume true crime content. Their
brains have been absolutely fried by
true crime and now they believe that
like every murder has a secret twist.
Every villain is simply misunderstood.
Not the detectives, not the FBI, not the
lawyers, not the police who have been
working on this for 3 years. No.
32-year-old Karen Smith from Ohio is
going to crack the case right after
Pilates. Trust me.
>> She He goes downstairs and he finds
>> Look at this beautiful house.
This is a person who doesn't have any
real problems.
If you live in a house this nice, you
don't probably have any real problems.
Not in the manifest direct way that
other people have real problems.
Like I'll say this about being a
streamer, right? I don't have real
problems other than like a handful of
like weird streamer related things.
Other people have real problems. You
live in that house. You don't have any
real problems.
>> Her like this, right? And she's
paralyzed. FIRST OF ALL, YOU'RE DEAD.
WELL, in Grey's Anatomy, they said
you're not dead until you're warm and
dead. can graze enough [laughter]
>> they said
>> oh my god
>> you agree right ma'am justice for Kora
Dawson and Ken three children that
Lindsay Clancy k
>> I think it's pretty easy to comment and
say a mother shouldn't kill her own kids
agree
>> yeah exactly why can't women say this
>> do you feel like men
>> are you a woman you should shut up
>> response to this trial has been fair
>> I don't think a man should have any say
in it honestly
>> for most of human evolutionary history
women had serious bi biological
investment in pregnancy and raising
children. They had to be extremely
attentive and aware of their social
environments and surroundings. Can I eat
these berries? Can my children eat these
berries? Who can I trust? How do I
maintain a safe relationship with my
community and the rest of the herd?
While men, on the other hand, are more
risk-taking, explorative, and had to
distinguish themselves from other male
competitors. This, of course, is
painting with a broader. This is why, by
the way, um, all of the male animals are
more attractive and appealing than
female animals.
Like a peacock, a male peacock versus a
female peacock. We've talked about this
a lot. I don't want to go through all of
it, but this is the reason why men are
more attractive than women.
>> Say,
>> it's not gay. It's the opposite of gay
>> here. This is not a bad thing. It's good
that women and men are different. That's
how society functions. of these
instincts are used for the wrong things.
Men's risk takingaking gets them into
deadly car crashes. A man's herd
mentality gets them into defending
Lindsay Clancy online.
>> Like I've seen women post about it, but
I guess like I don't know. He's the one
that did it.
>> Yeah. I don't know whether whether so
he's not on trial. He's never been
charged before.
>> No, but all the evidence I guess points
to him.
>> They the defense is saying she's the
killer.
>> Everybody knows she's not though.
[laughter]
It is important to remember that when
you are arguing with a woman, you are
not arguing with her. You are arguing
with the 145 Tik Toks she watched that
day. Normie women are having their
social media feeds flooded with other
women, their community, people they
trust, the herd talking about this
situation. Females telling other females
this is something they should care about
gives a sort of faux community and they
feel like they need to band together.
the sisterhood. Big part of this
instinct is the fear of social
ostriization from that sisterhood. You
do not want to be exiled from the herd.
You do not want to be kicked out of the
sisterhood. Well, jokes's on you. I'm
too autistic to care about any of that
Here comes tongue on boot to send
for the patriarchy.
>> Oh yeah, they they hated her for this.
Like Shu always gets hate by other
women.
Most of them are fat. I don't know if
there's a co coincidence there or not. I
just see they're a bunch of fat ugly
hoes getting mad over nothing.
>> Imagine needing male attention this bad.
Being a woman who doesn't support
Lindsay Clancy feels like being one of
the few gentlemen in the hood who didn't
support Carmelo Anthony. [laughter]
>> You pick me out here.
>> Breaking rank. Shame on you. It is
always always us against the men.
>> Look at this.
>> Dare you go rot with the rest of them.
I'm sorry I'm letting down the
sisterhood of the traveling SSRIs by not
supporting a murder. I [laughter] just
think all the berries you're eating are
poisonous and I think the herd is
running off a cliff.
>> Stop thinking about these kids as people
and think about them as ceramic vases.
>> No.
>> What? Why?
I mean, if you break a ceramic vase, you
can put it back together, right? You
can't do that with a kid. I'm pretty
sure you can't.
>> No, I will not do that actually. Now, if
you imagine all these dead prostitutes
in my freezer are actually ice cream
sandwiches, like
>> what? Excuse me. What?
>> I want you to think of these kids as if
they were very expensive ceramic vases
in a museum. And instead of thinking
about psychosis, we're going to think
about epilepsy. So, imagine that Lindsay
is in a museum and she is a person with
epilepsy. Weird how in the middle of
breaking all these ceramic vases while
having a seizure, she was able to take a
call from her husband while he was at
CVS and sound completely normal. Almost
like she wasn't having a seizure while
she was breaking these ceramic vases.
Apparently, same Lindsay was trending on
Tik Tok where women post themselves
holding their children with the caption,
"Same Lindsay." What do you mean same
Lindsay? The only implication there is
that you will one day do the same thing
she did. Is that what you were saying
here? Yeah, we should have CPSed all
these women. CPS them. Uh, take their
kids away, put them in a mental
institution, and everything will be
fine.
>> You are not Lindsay Clancy. You are
stressed out and you are sad. I
understand it's overwhelming sometimes,
but this will pass. Stop projecting
yourself onto a murderer. Postpartum
depression is absolutely a real thing. I
hate how this discourse has kind of
become like a debate whether or not it's
real. It's absolutely real. Women's
hormones are insane after they give
birth. They just like
>> uh all the time. But yeah,
>> drop off aing cliff. Things get pretty
bad. But for most women, like basically
all women have postpartum depression do
not in fact murder their children. But
here's the big thing with this entire
case. Uh she's full of Yeah. A forensic
psychologist assessed Lindsay over a
3-day period, and said that Lindsay has
bipolar disorder, has experienced no
manic episodes, was not manic when she
killed her children, never had
psychosis, postpartum or otherwise, no
hallucinations, meaning she lied about
hearing voices, maintained full
awareness during the crime, was in full
control of her actions, and understood
the illegality and moral wrongness of
her actions. In other words, she's a
lying ass your honor. Both her
PPD and PPP were self-dagnosed after all
of this. Psychosis. My entire fat white
ass. I do not buy it for a second. It's
like a non crazy person's idea of what a
crazy person would sound like in order
to get the insanity plea. Who the voices
the voices only spoke to me one time and
it was conveniently when the only person
who could protect the children was sent
out of the house by me. Whoa. I can't
say.
>> How convenient for her. What I want to
say because I will be banned off of
Weeny Hut Jr. tube. Andrea Yates drowned
her five children in a bathtub in 2001.
She had a long medical history of
depression, psychosis, and hearing
voices. She believed that she was evil
and the only way to save her children
from her was to [clears throat] kill
them. Andrea Yates had no public
support. Nobody was rallying for her
mental health, probably because there
was no social media back then to
convince a bunch of stupid hogs that she
was some kind of postbottom hero or
something.
>> Thank you. Thank you. You need to call
them hogs. That's what they are. That's
what they are. It's not It's again, it's
about the vocabulary. We talk about them
in the way that they are.
>> But during her legal proceedings, she
said she deserved punishment and wanted
to be punished for killing her children.
Compare that to Lindsay Clancy, who
allegedly immediately asked for a lawyer
and is trying her hardest to get a
lighter sentence. If I went crazy and
killed my children, I would not want to
be alive. This is so guilty. It's
crazy.
>> This young lady did nothing wrong in her
life. She was a nurse,
>> a daughter, a wife.
>> Yeah.
>> And a dang good mother.
>> Oh, she was a good girl.
>> No, I mean, not. I mean, if you kill the
kids, I feel like that makes you a bad
mom. Like, I mean, I feel like if you if
if I don't know, it's like saying that
you're a good driver if you crash a car.
I mean, that's I mean, not really,
though, right? I mean, like, damn.
>> He didn't do nothing.
>> This is a prosecution that has ripped
the soul out of this girl.
>> That girl literally ripped the soul out
of soul to begin with girl. But, okay.
There's no accountability ever. Ever.
Ever. No accountability whatsoever. You
could do the most evil thing on earth
and there's no accountability. It's not
your fault. It's not your fault. It's
the doctor's fault. It's your husband's
fault. You were let down. You're just a
perpetual victim of the universe. She's
just a girl, your honor. Holy. In the
book, The Goddess That Failed by Janice
Famango, Janice writes, "Women are
benign and men are dangerous. Even when
we are aware of women and men committing
similar violent acts, we interpret the
acts differently, imputing cruel motives
to men and helplessness to the women. We
excuse women's violence with emphasis on
emotional stress or mental illness.
>> The real reason why we do this is
because women's violence and women's
behavior is really of no consequence.
Like nobody really cares. Like some
woman has a crash out or something like
that. Doesn't matter. A guy has a crash
out and there's like 30 people that are
dead,
right? I mean like that's unless you're
a kid. Well, I mean like but it's
extremely rare and and honestly fathers
kill their kids all the time too, right?
Like overwhelmingly women women's
aggression isn't treated as seriously as
men's because it's not as consequential
as men's.
It's just the truth.
No consequences. These kids are dead.
Are you hearing yourself? You You seem
to be emotional.
You seem to be emotional about this. I'm
not emotional about this. You're not
listening to what's being discussed.
>> Women's violence is a cry for help.
Men's is assertion of power. As a
result, even when women harm the most
vulnerable among us, we are unwilling to
condemn the acts, fully punish the
perpetrators, or revise our belief in
female moral innocence. Also, every
other Tik Tok video supporting
Lindsay Clancy had the same song. I
can't post it because YouTube is
ridiculous, but I'll just try and sing
it. Everyday I'm a woman
[singing and music]
taking care of babies. I'm going crazy.
I got to do the dishes. you, dad. I
swear to God, I think the song is called
Labor by Never. Look it up. And it's
become like the psychotic woman national
anthem. These people are so dramatic and
corny. And while I was watching these
corny ass Tik Toks, all I kept thinking
about was the kids. How scared and
confused they probably were while their
own mother, the person that was supposed
to protect them, the person they trusted
betrayed them like that. Like, how do
you do that? One by one. And they're not
little kids. They're not all little
babies. like they struggled. Kids are so
innocent. Their world is so small. All
they know is this is the part we saw and
their toys and their safe home that was
just all taken from them in cold blood.
And like we're supposed to feel bad for
her. She's the real victim. She was sad.
We have to go wear pink and march for
her. No. All these women did was make a
murderer a millionaire and get America
closer to repealing the 19th. No,
serious.
>> Thank you. Thank you ladies. Thank you.
You'll Yeah. And and you'll you'll
you'll appreciate it
after this burden of suffering or sorry,
suffrage uh has been alleviated.
Uh you know, everything will be better.
Just trust me, you'll be fine. You'll be
so much happier. Because of this, repeal
the 19th was trending on Twitter for
like multiple days. Honestly, at this
point, if I have to give up my vote so
pitbull mama 78 also loses her vote,
that is a sacrifice. I am willing to
make.
>> So, as I am filming right now, the jury
has decided.
They haven't decided yet. Yeah. Awesome.
I don't know why the it's taken so
long. Maybe by the time you guys watch
this, they came to a conclusion, but
right now there is none.
>> Over 24 hours of deliberations and still
no way in the Lindsay Clancy murder
trial. If the jury remains deadlocked, a
retrial is still possible. Also, some
crazy woman named Dawn Light, a Clancy
supporter and quote crime junkie, was
just arrested for yelling at the jury.
So, this is just an absolute
>> I feel like if you're a crime junkie,
you should know that you can't with
the the jury, right? You shouldn't just
know this
>> circus. And I have no idea what is going
to happen. In conclusion, Lindsay Clancy
admitted she did it. There's no evidence
her husband did it. She was never
diagnosed with postpartum psychosis. She
had plenty resources. She had tons of
help. She purposely told her husband to
go on a long errand so she could do what
she wanted to. She was not failed by the
system. She failed herself. And most of
all, she failed those children. She
betrayed them like an evil demonic
from hell. She deserves to rot in prison
or worse. So that was that video. That
is my opinion. Subscribe if you liked
this video and you agree.
based by the way. I totally ag
totally agree with everything she's
saying. Like it's actually such a huge
problem that people are sitting on
social media agreeing with each other
like this. And I think that now like I'm
glad that this has happened because now
you have more people discussing the
biological differences in thinking.
There's always been like a stigma at
least as long as I've been alive about
acknowledging that there are differences
in people that are not visual.
like any sort of acknowledgment that
thinking is different, IQ is different,
temperament is different, emotions are
different. This has always been a
forbidden topic.
Finally, now that's stopping. And and
now we're talking about it again, which
is good
with me. If you didn't argue in the
comments, I don't know. What do you
think of this? And yeah, um I love you
guys. Take care of yourselves. log off.
Go touch grass and I will see you next
time.
>> Wow.
I got to link you guys this video. What
an insanely good video. Sorry, I'm
hungry. I'm eating beef jerky. It
happened the other way around. No sane
woman would be calling for that man if
he was ugly to be Charlie Kirk. Yeah, of
course.
Yeah, there's the video. Make sure to
give it a like. I mean, I agree with
everything that she's been saying. I
feel like everybody knew that she was
going to make a video about this and
it's like, yeah, it was that good. It
[snorts] was insanely good. I
wish that more people realized how bad
this is. Men will make the gender war.
I think that there's always been like
there there will there will always be a
problem with something like that as long
as you have people that are making
excuses and stopping this bad behavior.
She's great. Yes, she is. Do you think
if she was black that she would have
gotten the same support? No.
Um, I think that white women see
themselves in her and because she's
white and they're white, I think that
she would have received different
support. I think that a person's
identity is crucial and foundational to
the way that they get supported on
social media. Most people are just tribe
animals. They are they're just tribe
animals. That's it. There's no
complication to it. It's not hard to
understand. It's just that simple.
I eat my food real quick.
You ever realize I breed like a hog and
I indulge in beef jerky? It's because I
talk and eat at the same time. That's
why
white women are the most privileged
people ever in the West. No. White women
are the priv White in the West are the
most privileged class of people of all
time in all of history. And it's not
even remotely close. It's actually
insane.
That's why you gag. Yeah, sure. And uh
yeah, if you eat, boy, I can't. I I have
to. I just whenever I'm streaming, this
is why I don't like to eat during
stream, but I just get hungry sometimes.
I have to. I'm move away from me.
Worst sounds. I know.
I'm sorry, guys.
You got to eat, bro. Yeah.
Anyway, so yes, E burger. Yeah, sure.
And spoiled white men just want to be
the biggest victim in the room. Well,
there's one group they try and one up
each other's trauma. Yeah, of course.
And and the reason and and that's why
they've invented all these mental
disorders for themselves, right? It's
because they want to feel oppressed.
They want to feel like the world is
against them and they are victims and
they are minorities and they have some
solidarity because one way that you can
really hack people's psychology is you
play into guilt. Like if you play into
guilt with a woman, it almost always
works because it just hijacks their
brain. like e each individual person
that you know like each person that you
deal with you have to understand that
like you know you have to take there's
like different boss mechanics for each
person
>> basically same with the gender
identities. Yeah it is.
>> White women's podcast reinforce this
delusion. Well, it's a self it's a
self-reinforcing paradigm, right?